export const chapter = "Chapter - 2: Clothes to Wear";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Why do we wear clothes?",
        optionA: "To look fashionable",
        optionB: "To protect our body from the elements",
        optionC: "To show off our wealth",
        correctAnswer: "To protect our body from the elements",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the purpose of wearing woollen clothes in winters?",
        optionA: "To look fashionable",
        optionB: "To stay warm and comfortable",
        optionC: "To show off to friends",
        correctAnswer: "To stay warm and comfortable",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is not a woollen clothing item mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Sweater",
        optionB: "Jeans",
        optionC: "Woollen cap",
        correctAnswer: "Jeans",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which type of clothes are preferred in summers according to the text?",
        optionA: "Leather jackets",
        optionB: "Cotton clothes",
        optionC: "Raincoats",
        correctAnswer: "Cotton clothes",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What do we wear when we need to go out in the rain to stay dry?",
        optionA: "Sunglasses",
        optionB: "Raincoat and gumboots",
        optionC: "Sandals",
        correctAnswer: "Raincoat and gumboots",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When do people wear fancy or party clothes, according to the text?",
        optionA: "When they go to work",
        optionB: "When they attend a party",
        optionC: "When they stay at home",
        correctAnswer: "When they attend a party",
      },
      {
        question: "Why do many persons wear uniforms to their work?",
        optionA: "To save money on buying regular clothes",
        optionB: "To show their individuality",
        optionC: "To represent their occupation or organization",
        correctAnswer: "To represent their occupation or organization",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What type of clothing do watchmen, policemen, and postmen typically wear, as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Formal suits",
        optionB: "Uniforms",
        optionC: "Casual attire",
        correctAnswer: "Uniforms",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the main purpose of wearing raincoats, gumboots, and carrying an umbrella in the rain?",
        optionA: "To show off in front of others",
        optionB: "To stay warm",
        optionC: "To protect from getting wet",
        correctAnswer: "To protect from getting wet",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What do cotton clothes protect us from in summers, according to the text?",
        optionA: "Excessive sunlight",
        optionB: "Cold weather",
        optionC: "Heat",
        correctAnswer: "Heat",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "We wear clothes to cover our ________.",
        optionA: "Shoes",
        optionB: "Body",
        optionC: "Toys",
        correctAnswer: "Body",
      },
      {
        question: "Clothes protect us from ________, ________, and ________.",
        optionA: "Laughter, sadness, excitement",
        optionB: "Heat, cold, rain",
        optionC: "Trees, animals, buildings",
        correctAnswer: "Heat, cold, rain",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In winters, we wear woollen clothes like sweater, jacket, gloves, woollen cap, and muffler to stay ________.",
        optionA: "Wet",
        optionB: "Cold",
        optionC: "Warm",
        correctAnswer: "Warm",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In summers, we prefer to wear cotton clothes such as shirt, pants, frock, skirt, and top to stay ________.",
        optionA: "Dry",
        optionB: "Hot",
        optionC: "Cool",
        correctAnswer: "Cool",
      },
      {
        question:
          "To protect ourselves from getting wet in the rain, we wear a raincoat and gumboots and carry an umbrella. These items protect us from getting ________.",
        optionA: "Tired",
        optionB: "Wet",
        optionC: "Hungry",
        correctAnswer: "Wet",
      },
      {
        question: "We wear fancy or party clothes when we attend a ________.",
        optionA: "School",
        optionB: "Park",
        optionC: "Party",
        correctAnswer: "Party",
      },
      {
        question: "Many persons wear uniforms to their ________.",
        optionA: "Bedroom",
        optionB: "Work",
        optionC: "Playground",
        correctAnswer: "Work",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Watchmen, policemen, and postmen typically wear ________ to their work.",
        optionA: "Uniforms",
        optionB: "Casual clothes",
        optionC: "Costumes",
        correctAnswer: "Uniforms",
      },
      {
        question: "Our choice for clothes depends on ________.",
        optionA: "The moon's phase",
        optionB: "Occasions",
        optionC: "Our shoe size",
        correctAnswer: "Occasions",
      },
      {
        question: "We wear ________ when we go to school.",
        optionA: "Raincoats",
        optionB: "Uniform",
        optionC: "Party clothes",
        correctAnswer: "Uniform",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "We wear clothes to cover our body.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Clothes protect us from heat, cold, and rain.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "We wear woollen clothes in summers.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Cotton clothes are preferred in winters.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Raincoat and gumboots protect us from getting wet in the rain.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "We always wear fancy or party clothes when attending a party.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Uniforms are typically worn to school.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Many persons wear uniforms to their work.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Our choice for clothes depends solely on the seasons.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "We wear raincoats and gumboots in the summer.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
